<rss version="2.0" 
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/">
    
    <channel>
	<title>GEO TV - Business</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.geo.tv/rss/1/0" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.geo.tv/</link>
	<description>GeoTV, Geo News, Latest-News, Breaking News, Pakistan, Live Videos</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 15:50:07 +0500</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Unilever prepares 6 billion pound sale of food brands]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134848-Unilever-prepares-6-billion-pound-sale-of-food-brands?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 20:07:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134848-Unilever-prepares-6-billion-pound-sale-of-food-brands?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134848_080718_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Unilever is preparing a 6 billion pound ($7.44 billion) sale of some of its food brands, British newspapers reported on Saturday.</strong></p>
<p>The Anglo-Dutch company is planning to sell Flora margarine and Stork butter brands, the Sunday Times said.</p>
<p>The Sunday Telegraph, which also cited a 6 billion pounds figure, cited sources as saying private equity firms Bain Capital, CVC and Clayton Dubilier and Rice have started working on offers for the "spreads" business, citing sources.</p>
<p>Unilever did not immediately respond to a Reuters request for comment.</p>
<p>The maker of Knorr soups, Dove soap and Ben &amp; Jerry's ice cream rebuffed a surprise $143 billion takeover offer from Kraft Heinz &nbsp;last month.</p>
<p>The company has launched a business review to consider returning cash to shareholders, making medium-sized acquisitions and more aggressive cost cuts, the Financial Times reported on Wednesday.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Erdogan accuses Merkel of using ´Nazi measures´]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134847-Erdogan-accuses-Merkel-of-using-Nazi-measures?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 19:58:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134847-Erdogan-accuses-Merkel-of-using-Nazi-measures?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134847_075900_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISTANBUL. Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan on Sunday launched a scathing personal attack against German Chancellor Angela Merkel, accusing her of using "Nazi measures" in an intensifying dispute between Ankara and Berlin.</strong><br /> Tensions flared after German authorities refused to allow some Turkish ministers to campaign for a &acute;yes&acute; vote in the April 16 referendum on expanding Erdogan&acute;s powers, and he responded by saying Berlin was behaving like Nazi Germany.&nbsp;<br /> "When we call them Nazis they (Europe) get uncomfortable. They rally together in solidarity. Especially Merkel," Erdogan said in a televised speech.<br /> "But you are right now employing Nazi measures," Erdogan told Merkel using the informal &acute;you&acute; in Turkish.&nbsp;<br /> "Against who? My Turkish brother citizens in Germany and brother ministers" who went to the country to hold campaign rallies for a &acute;yes&acute; vote in next month&acute;s referendum.<br /> Authorities in Germany have blocked some Turkish ministers from holding rallies, infuriating Ankara.<br /> Erdogan said the crisis in relations with Europe over the last days "showed that a new page had been opened in the ongoing fight against our country."<br /> Accusing Europe of backing outlawed terror groups, he warned: "The masked ball is over!" without specifying further.<br /> Turkey had earlier expressed fury that German authorities had on Saturday allowed a pro-Kurdish demonstration in Frankfurt to go ahead where many participants carried insignia of the outlawed Kurdistan Workers Party (PKK).<br /> Germany meanwhile is livid over the jailing ahead of a trial on terror charges of dual Turkish-German national Deniz Yucel, the Turkey correspondent of the German newspaper Die Welt.<br /> Erdogan described Yucel, whose arrest has caused global concern, as a "terror agent" and "supposed journalist" and accused Germany of hosting him for one month at its Istanbul consulate before he went to police for questioning.&nbsp;<br /> </p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Aamir Khan reportedly paid Rs1.75 billion for Dangal]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134843-Aamir-Khan-reportedly-paid-Rs175-billion-for-Dangal?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 19:13:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134843-Aamir-Khan-reportedly-paid-Rs175-billion-for-Dangal?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134843_071955_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Bollywood perfectionist Aamir Khan, who turned 52 last week, is still hiding high from the success of his last venture, Dangal.</strong></p>
<p>The feature, which was based on a real life story of two female wrestlers, is reported to have earned Rs5.32 billion in national and international markets.</p>
<p>Aamir Khan&rsquo;s efforts to make the movie a success have not gone unpaid and he got a hefty sum of Rs1.75billion for the movie, according to Indian media.</p>
<p>Aamir Khan is one of the few Bollywood actors who use the profit sharing technique to get paid. He charges producers about 33 per cent of the movie&rsquo;s profit.</p>
<p>An industry insider revealed that the actor took Rs0.35 billion upfront and will take 33 percent of the movie&rsquo;s profit.</p>
<p>The actor will be seen in an extended cameo in his home production, Secret Superstar. Zaira Wasim, who played his daughter in Dangal, is the movie&rsquo;s lead.</p>
<p><em>&nbsp;</em></p>
<p><em>*Converting the sum to Pakistan Rupee will make it about Rs2.8 billion</em></p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Returned to face allegations, says defiant Sharjeel Memon]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134839-Returned-to-face-allegations-says-defiant-Sharjeel-Memon?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 18:57:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134839-Returned-to-face-allegations-says-defiant-Sharjeel-Memon?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134839_065800_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISLAMABAD: Pakistan Peoples' Party senior leader Sharjeel Memon&nbsp;on Sunday said that he came back to Pakistan to face the allegations against him, as he is not the one to run away from problems.</strong></p>
<p>Memon, who was recently released after a brief detention by the National Accountability Bureau from Islamabad airport, was holding a press conference in the capital.</p>
<p>&ldquo;I wasn&rsquo;t arrested at the airport, I was abducted,&rdquo; he said.</p>
<p>He said that he was going abroad for medical purposes and had prior permission from Chief Minister Sindh Murad Ali Shah.</p>
<p>He said that all of a sudden his name was put on the Exit Control List, following which he contacted the Sindh High Court over the matter.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Putting my name on the ECL is an extreme measure,&rdquo; said Memon.</p>
<p>The PPP leader said that a reference was&nbsp;filed against him, although the SHC approved his bail.</p>
<p>&ldquo;For the PPP, the law of the country is entirely different,&rdquo; he said.</p>
<p>The allegations are equally embarrassing for the party, said the PPP leader.</p>
<p>Memon was taken into custody from Islamabad airport by the NAB personnel immediately after his arrival from Dubai. Memon arrived in the country along with the Sindh ministers, Mukesh Chawla, Imdad Pitafi, Fayyaz Ali Butt and Nawab Taimur Talpur.</p>
<p>According to sources privy to the development, six plain-cloth personnel under the deputy director of NAB's crime wing took Memon into their custody from Benazir Bhutto International Airport on the advice of NAB`s Karachi division immediately when he came outside from the flight, EK-614. The provincial legislator was shifted to an undisclosed location. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sharjeel Memon is scheduled to appear before the court on Monday.</p>
<p>NAB has filed a reference against Memon and 10 others in an accountability court of Karachi for alleged corruption of around Rs5.76billion.</p>
<p>Besides Memon, other accused include Zulfiqar Ali Shallwani, Aneeta Baloch, Mansoor Ahmed Rajput, Mohammad Yousuf Kaboro, Inaam Akbar, Altaf Hussain Memon, Riyaz Manir, Fazal Mehmood, Mohammad Hanif, Asim, Masood Hashmi, Gulzar Ali, Suleman Mansoor Umer, Syed Naveed and Sarang Latif Chandio.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Memon was living in a self-imposed exile for more than two years in Dubai and London.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Sharjeel’s detention despite court orders baffles CM Sindh]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134840-Sharjeels-detention-despite-court-orders-baffles-CM-Sindh?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 18:56:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134840-Sharjeels-detention-despite-court-orders-baffles-CM-Sindh?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134840_070408_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>HYDERABAD: Chief Minister Sindh Murad Ali Shah on Sunday strongly criticised the brief detention of Pakistan People&rsquo;s Party (PPP) senior leader Sharjeel Memon, saying that politically motivated interference of institutions will not be tolerated.</strong></p>
<p>Talking to the media after visiting a power project in Nooriabad, he said that Sharjeel Memon returned after getting permission from Islamabad High Court.</p>
<p>&ldquo;The court had ordered that Sharjeel Memon should not be arrested before a hearing in court&rdquo;, he added.</p>
<p>He alleged that only PPP members were being targeted and had Memon been called, he would&rsquo;ve appeared himself.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We have always respected courts. Sharjeel would appear before the court tomorrow and we will accept the decision of the court&rdquo;, he added.</p>
<p>Talking about the detention of Farooq Sattar, CM Sindh said that MQM Pakistan leader was not arrested, as per his information.</p>
<p>He said warrants against Sattar were issued many months ago but he never got bail for them.</p>
<p>On Sunday morning, Memon was released after being briefly detained by the National Accountability Bureau from Islamabad airport.</p>
<p>Memon spoke to his family members and the chief minister of Sindh after being released.</p>
<p>NAB released the former provincial informational minister after getting verification and undertaking on his bail before arrest from his lawyer Shakeel Abbasi.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Indian delegation reaches Lahore for PIC meeting]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134804-Indian-delegation-to-reach-Lahore-today-for-PIC-meeting?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 17:13:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134804-Indian-delegation-to-reach-Lahore-today-for-PIC-meeting?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134804_095152_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>LAHORE: An Indian delegation reached Lahore through the Wagah border on Sunday to take part in the Permanent Indus Commission (PIC) meeting, beginning March 20 in Islamabad.</strong></p>
<p>The 10-member delegation, which will take part in the two-day meeting, comprises India's Indus Water Commissioner PK Saxena, MEA officials and technical experts.</p>
<p>During the talks, the three ongoing projects on River Chenab will come under discussion.</p>
<p>According to experts, India has violated the Indus Water Treaty by constructing five large dams. The country has plans to construct a total of 262 dams by 2025 on Pakistan and Kashmir's water sources.</p>
<p>The 57-year old pact assigned River Ravi, Beas, and Sutlej to India whereas River Chenab, Jehlum, and Sindh were allocated to Pakistan.</p>
<p>As per the agreement, both countries are liable to hold deliberations each year in order to ensure compliance with the treaty and resolve any disputes.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Bangladesh secure first win against Sri Lanka in 100th test]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134829-Bangladesh-secure-first-win-against-Sri-Lanka-in-100th-test?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 17:02:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134829-Bangladesh-secure-first-win-against-Sri-Lanka-in-100th-test?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134829_050228_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>COLOMBO. Bangladesh secured their maiden Test win against Sri Lanka with a four-wicket victory on the final day of the second Test at the P Sara Oval on Sunday.</strong></p>
<p>Playing their 100th match in the longest format of the game, the touring side chased down their target of 191 in the final session to level the two-match series at 1-1.</p>
<p>Captain Mushfiqur Rahim was unbeaten on 22 while Mehedi Hasan was not out on two after hitting the winning runs.</p>
<p>Bangladesh set a target of 191 for a series-levelling win against Sri Lanka on the final day of the second test after the hosts were all out for 319 in their second innings on Sunday.<br /> Dilruwan Perera was run out after scoring a 50 but not before he had added 80 for the ninth wicket with Suranga Lakmal, who became the final wicket to fall in the morning after his highest test score of 42.Left-arm spinner Shakib Al Hasan picked up 4-74 for Bangladesh.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Mustafa Kamal says Pakistan can't operate without Karachi]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134822-Mustafa-Kamal-says-Pakistan-cant-operate-without-Karachi?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 15:23:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134822-Mustafa-Kamal-says-Pakistan-cant-operate-without-Karachi?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134822_032704_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: Addressing an event at a local hall, Pak Sar Zameen Party (PSP) chief Mustafa Kamal said Pakistan can't operate without Karachi.</strong></p>
<p>"A solution to Karachi's problems is the solution to Pakistan's problems," said Kamal. "The government must facilitate the business community."</p>
<p>The former Muttahida Qaumi Movement (MQM) party member said the number of votes in favour of Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf (PTI) in 2013's elections reflected the hatred for MQM founder Altaf Hussain.</p>
<p>"Criminals suit him [Altaf Hussain]. He continues to make efforts to turn Muhajirs against members of other ethnicities."</p>
<p>He blamed the party founder for the downfall of MQM and Muhajirs.</p>
<p>"We [PSP] won't accept charity, donations or zakat," said Kamal. "We will dissolve the party the day we take a single wrong action."</p>
<p>"The government should focus on making the process of population census transparent," he said.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Japan agrees to fund exclusive bus service for women in KP]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134821-Japan-agrees-to-fund-exclusive-bus-service-for-women?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 14:43:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134821-Japan-agrees-to-fund-exclusive-bus-service-for-women?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134821_025537_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>PESHAWAR: The Japanese government approved aid to start an exclusive bus service for female passengers in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa (KP).</strong></p>
<p>The request to the Japanese government for funding of the project was made in what seems to be the provincial government's attempt to resolve severe commuting issues faced by female passengers due to the conservative Pashtun culture.</p>
<p>The KP government will allocate 7 of the 13 buses to Peshawar, while 3 buses each will be allocated to Mardan and Abbottabad.</p>
<p>The authorities will consider the possibility of hiring female conductors for the service, which is yet to be named.</p>
<p>Only female passengers and children below the age of 12 will be allowed to travel on the bus service, which is likely to be named &ldquo;Pink Buses&rdquo; a source said.</p>
<p>Talking to Geo News, an official said that each bus would have 40 seats and approximately cost PKR 8.5 million. &nbsp;</p>
<p>The service is likely to begin in August this year. &nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Two children injured in unprovoked Indian firing at LoC]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134819-Two-children-injured-in-unprovoked-Indian-firing-at-LoC?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 14:22:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134819-Two-children-injured-in-unprovoked-Indian-firing-at-LoC?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134819_022236_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISLAMABAD: Innocent civilians were targeted yet again in unprovoked firing by Indian forces along the Line of Control on Saturday night, Foreign Office spokesperson Nafees Zakaria informed.</strong></p>
<p>Taking to Twitter earlier today, the FO spokesperson said two children aged 9 and 14 were injured in the firing, which was carried out at Nakyal and Balakot sectors at 9:50 pm on Saturday.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Unprovoked <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CFVbyIndia?src=hash">#CFVbyIndia</a> again targeted innocent civilians at LoC Nikial Sec Balakot vill injuring children aged 9 &amp; 14 at 2150 hrs yesterday</p>
&mdash; M. Nafees Zakaria (@ForeignOfficePk) <a href="https://twitter.com/ForeignOfficePk/status/843380295739084801">March 19, 2017</a></blockquote>
<p>Indian forces on Saturday also resorted to unprovoked firing in Kot Kehtera sector along the LoC, as a result of which a 60-year-old woman in village Thandi Kassi was martyred, Inter-Services Public Relations said in a statement.</p>
<p>Pakistani troops, however, gave a befitting response to the unprovoked fire and silenced the enemy guns, the ISPR said. This was the third ceasefire violation by the Indian forces in less than 10 days.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Aamir Khan names MQM-London leaders, ‘Chamchagir Brigade’]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134796-Aamir-Khan-names-MQM-London-leaders-Chamchagir-Brigade?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 13:55:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134796-Aamir-Khan-names-MQM-London-leaders-Chamchagir-Brigade?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134796_124850_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: Speaking at MQM-Pakistan's Youm-e-Tasees, senior leader Amir Khan expressed his disapproval for the MQM-London leadership.</strong></p>
<p>Khan named London-based party leaders Wasy Jalil, Babar Ghauri, Imbisat Mallick, Mustufa Azizabadi, and Muhammad Anwar as, &lsquo;chamchagir brigade.&rsquo;</p>
<p>He claimed that former minister of ports and shipping Babar Ghauri owns as many as 31 petrol pumps in the city.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Babar Ghauri, who owns properties worth millions of dollars in America, owns 31 petrol stations here in Karachi. Did he inherit this fortune from his father?&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;He has run away from Pakistan after looting vast fortunes, and he should give this money back to party workers.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Without naming the MQM-Pakistan founder, Khan thundered: &ldquo;It&rsquo;s you, not us who is the&nbsp;traitor. You have always left the workers on their own in difficult times.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Disgusting language is being used against Pakistan by Wasay Jalil,&rdquo; alleged Khan. &ldquo;If you (Jalil) have any courage, come here to Pakistan and then chant these slogans. We will see how brave you are then.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Khan jibed at his former leader through a comment on the late Benazir Bhutto's bravery, who he said arrived in Pakistan to be with her voters despite being aware of the impending threats.</p>
<p>Khan concluded his speech by saying: &ldquo;There comes a time when one has to decide between the country and individual personalities.&rdquo;&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Babar Ghauri refutes Amir Khan's allegations]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134817-Babar-Ghauri-refutes-Amir-Khans-allegations?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 13:25:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134817-Babar-Ghauri-refutes-Amir-Khans-allegations?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134817_013652_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: Former Minister for Ports and Shipping Babar Khan Ghauri on Sunday dismissed the allegations made by Muttahida Qaumi Movement (MQM) Pakistan leader Amir Khan.</strong></p>
<p>Ghauri refuted Khan's allegation of the former owning 31 petrol stations. "I would like the MQM-Pakistan leader to provide evidence to back his claim," said the formal federal minister.</p>
<p>The former minister said the public is being distracted by political rhetoric instead of elected officials taking concrete steps to resolve their problems.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Talking to Geo News, Ghauri said: "I don't wish to engage in mudslinging but I have the right to take legal action against such allegations."</p>
<p>Speaking at MQM Pakistan's Youm-e-Tasees yesterday, Khan claimed that Ghauri owns as many as 31 petrol pumps in Karachi.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Babar Ghauri, who owns properties of millions of dollars in American, owns 31 petrol pumps here in Karachi. Did he inherit it from his father?&rdquo; he said. &ldquo;He should give the money to the worker, he has run away after looting from here.&rdquo;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Faryal says she thought marriage with boxer Amir Khan would be a ‘fairytale’]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134815-Faryal-says-she-thought-marriage-with-boxer-Amir-Khan-would-be-a-fairytale?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:51:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134815-Faryal-says-she-thought-marriage-with-boxer-Amir-Khan-would-be-a-fairytale?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134815_125127_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Looks like Faryal Makhdoom, the model wife of British boxer of Pakistani origin Amir Khan, just cannot seem to stay away from the headlines for long.</strong></p>
<p>Merely a few weeks after the vicious, long-running public spat between the 25-year-old Faryal and 30-year-old Amir&rsquo;s parents and siblings, the glamour girl is back, this time claiming that she thought her marriage with Amir Khan would be a &ldquo;fairytale&rdquo; (quite a long shot, what with the toxic family feud and all).</p>
<p>&ldquo;In my head, living with my new husband was going to be this fairytale,&rdquo; she said in an interview to Daily Mail.</p>
<p>&ldquo;But it was hard and I didn&rsquo;t have any friends. Bolton is very backward. Compared to New York, it&rsquo;s a village,&rdquo; said Faryal, who moved to England from New York to live with her husband after marrying him in 2013.</p>
<p>Faryal also rebutted reports that she had had plastic surgery. Instead, she told the publication, she had resorted to &lsquo;fillers&rsquo;.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Because of lack of sleep, genes, dehydration, I get bags under my eyes and I wanted to get them lightened. So I went to my doctor, Simon [Ourian, a renowned cosmetic surgeon in LA] &ndash; he&rsquo;s also Kim Kardashian&rsquo;s doctor,&rdquo; she explained.</p>
<p>She also went for fillers in her cheeks because she &ldquo;likes high cheekbones&rdquo; &ndash; something for which she came under fire from her in-laws who likened her to Michael Jackson.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/faryal%20(1).jpg" alt="Faryal with her in-laws" width="100%" height="100%" /></p>
<p>&ldquo;If other women had this money and if they had a husband who was famous, they would do it, too. If I wasn&rsquo;t married to Amir Khan, I&rsquo;d probably be a regular girl and I might not do it. But I&rsquo;m in the limelight, I go to events, so it&rsquo;s part of my life now,&rdquo; the Daily Mail quoted her as saying.</p>
<p>Faryal also expressed her concerns on showing too much skin in pictures, saying she is a &ldquo;Muslim woman, so [she&rsquo;d] like to be covered up&rdquo;, although she has steadfastly defended her Western dressing against her in-laws&rsquo; criticisms.</p>
<p>The couple and their families were thrown into the limelight when Faryal took to social media last year accusing her in-laws of subjecting her to verbal abuse and criticising her for her &lsquo;modern&rsquo; way of dressing and living.</p>
<p>The accusations triggered a war of words between her and the boxer&rsquo;s family, with Amir Khan caught in the crosshairs. The situation became all the more embarrassing for the couple when an &lsquo;inappropriate&rsquo; video tape of the boxer emerged, intensifying the feud.</p>
<p>The couple currently resides in a rented apartment in San Francisco, where Amir Khan is training for a comeback fight later this year.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Are Deepika, Rajnikanth going to share screen together again?]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134812-Are-Deepika-Rajnikanth-going-to-share-screen-together-again?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:05:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134812-Are-Deepika-Rajnikanth-going-to-share-screen-together-again?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134812_120945_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p>Deepika and Rajinikanth together? Not happening anymore.</p>
<p>For the last couple of days, the internet was abuzz with the news that superstar Rajinikanth and Deepika Padukone which were last seen together in motion capture film&nbsp;Kochadaiiyaan, will reunite for Kabali director&rsquo;s next.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/default.jpg" alt="" width="480" height="238" /></p>
<p>While speculations were being made, the film&rsquo;s director Pa. Ranjith made a timely intervention and clarified that the news was just a rumour.</p>
<p>The director clarified the news on his Twitter account.</p>
<p>Earlier, it was also rumored that Radhika Apte was being considered for the same role.</p>
<p>Ranjith and Rajinikanth reunite after last year's Tamil blockbuster 'Kabali'.</p>
<p>Ranjith, however, has been working on the script for the last few months. Apparently, he had locked the first draft long back.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Person in custody after incident at White House gates: Secret Service]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134807-Person-in-custody-after-incident-at-White-House-gates-Secret-Service?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 11:01:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134807-Person-in-custody-after-incident-at-White-House-gates-Secret-Service?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134807_110146_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>One person was in custody after a suspicious vehicle drove up to a White House checkpoint on Saturday night, the Secret Service said, after CNN reported that the driver claimed to have a bomb.</strong></p>
<p>CNN, citing two law enforcement sources, said there was no confirmation of any device in the vehicle but that security at the White House had been upgraded.</p>
<p>The Secret Service said an unidentified driver was taken into custody after a suspicious vehicle approached a checkpoint, but made no mention of any claims of an explosive device.</p>
<p>Several streets around the White House were closed.</p>
<p>Other authorities could not be reached immediately to confirm more details.</p>
<p>It was the second scare at the White House on Saturday after a person earlier jumped over a bike rack in a buffer zone in front of the White House.</p>
<p>US President Donald Trump was in Florida at the time of both incidents.</p>
<p>In the first incident, the unidentified person was not able to make it over the fence into the grounds, White House spokesman Sean Spicer said on Twitter.</p>
<p>Two Secret Service agents reportedly tackled the individual in that incident, which occurred at the start of a buffer zone between the main White House fence and the sidewalks.</p>
<p>The Secret Service had been criticized after it said a man who scaled the White House fence last week was on the property's grounds for 16 minutes before being detained.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Pakistan Day parade: Armed Forces hold full dress rehearsal in Islamabad]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134805-Pakistan-Day-parade-Armed-Forces-hold-full-dress-rehearsal-in-Islamabad?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 10:31:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134805-Pakistan-Day-parade-Armed-Forces-hold-full-dress-rehearsal-in-Islamabad?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134805_103153_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISLAMABAD: A full dress rehearsal for the Pakistan Day parade is currently underway at the Shakarparian ground in the federal capital, Geo News reported.</strong></p>
<p>Contingents of the Pakistan Armed Forces are taking part in the rehearsal for the March 23 parade, which will see participation of three international forces this year.</p>
<p>According to reports, mobile phone services in Rawalpindi and Islamabad will remain suspended from 6am to 1pm due to the rehearsal.</p>
<p>Islamabad traffic police has also released the traffic plan for March 23 and rehearsal days. The route from Zero Point to Faizabad road will be closed from 6am to 1pm every day.</p>
<p>People's Liberation Army (PLA) China&rsquo;s Tri-Services and Saudi Special Force&rsquo;s contingents and Turkish Janissary Military band (Mehteran) are set to take part in the Pakistan Day parade, the ISPR said earlier this month.</p>
<p>Among other dignitaries, Chief of South African National Defence Force, General Solly Zacharia Shoke will also witness the parade.</p>
<p>Pakistan Day is a national holiday to commemorate the Lahore Resolution of March 23, 1940, when the Muslim League drafted the political resolution calling for establishing an independent federation.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Vast Beatles collection goes on auction in Paris]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134802-Vast-Beatles-collection-goes-on-auction-in-Paris?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 09:36:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134802-Vast-Beatles-collection-goes-on-auction-in-Paris?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134802_093651_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>A vast collection of rare Beatles vinyl records, photos and other paraphernalia went on auction in Paris on Saturday.</strong></p>
<p>Beatles aficionado Jacques Volcouve began his collection in 1967 with the album "A Hard Day's Night". Decades later, it has grown to include nearly 15,000 records and more besides.</p>
<p>"Starting from 1967, I gave myself an absolutely impossible mission: own everything concerning the Beatles," Volcouve told Reuters TV, as he was sorting through his collection December.</p>
<p>The 60-year-old has decided to auction off his collection to fund his retirement.</p>
<p>Among the 332 lots up for auction on Saturday is the disc "Tony Sheridan and the Beatles 7: My Bonnie," signed by Paul McCartney and George Harrison, with an estimated price of 6,000-10,000 euro ($6,450-10,740).</p>
<p>A lot of 11 alternate cover photos for the Grammy-winning Sergeant Pepper Lonely Hearts Club album is expected to go for 10,000 to 15,000 euros.</p>
<p>Volcouve has written books and given radio commentaries about the Liverpool foursome. Letters he received from Harrison and Ringo Starr in 1976, thanking him for articles he had written, could fetch up to 3,000 euros each.</p>
<p>A set of dolls of the Fab Four with their instruments is expected to sell for 200-400 euros.</p>
<p>Among other items up for sale are an "authentic Beatle wig", a Yoko Ono/John Lennon wedding album box and posters.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Rock 'n' roll pioneer Chuck Berry dead at 90]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134800-Rock-n-roll-pioneer-Chuck-Berry-dead-at-90?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 08:37:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134800-Rock-n-roll-pioneer-Chuck-Berry-dead-at-90?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134800_083826_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Chuck Berry, who duck-walked his way into the pantheon of rock 'n' roll pioneers as one of its most influential guitarists and lyricists, creating raucous anthems that defined the genre's sound and heartbeat, died on Saturday at his Missouri home. He was 90.</strong></p>
<p>Police in St. Charles County, outside St. Louis, said they were called to Berry's home by a caretaker and found him unresponsive. Efforts to revive him failed and he was pronounced dead at 1:26 p.m. local time.</p>
<p>Considered one of the founding fathers of rock 'n' roll, Charles Edward Anderson Berry was present at its infancy in the 1950s and emerged as its first star guitarist and songwriter - a nearly 30-year-old black performer whose style electrified young white audiences and was emulated by white performers who came to dominate American popular music.</p>
<p>Although Elvis Presley was called the king of rock 'n' roll, that crown would have fit just as well on Berry's own carefully sculpted pompadour.</p>
<p>Berry hits such as "Johnny B. Goode," "Roll Over Beethoven," "Sweet Little Sixteen," "Maybellene" and "Memphis" melded elements of blues, rockabilly and jazz into some of the most timeless pop songs of the 20th century.</p>
<p>He was a monumental influence on just about any kid who picked up a guitar with rock star aspirations - Keith Richards, Paul McCartney, John Lennon and Bruce Springsteen among them.</p>
<p>Bob Dylan called Berry "the Shakespeare of rock 'n' roll," and he was one of the first popular acts to write as well as perform his own songs. They focused on youth, romance, cars and good times, with lyrics that were complex, humorous and sometimes a little raunchy.</p>
<p>Both the Beatles and the Rolling Stones, as well as the Beach Boys and scores of other acts - even Elvis - covered Berry's songs.</p>
<p>"If you tried to give rock 'n' roll another name," Lennon once said, "you might call it 'Chuck Berry'."</p>
<p>Paying tribute to Berry on Twitter on Saturday, Springsteen called him "rock's greatest practitioner, guitarist, and the greatest pure rock 'n' roll writer who ever lived." Rolling Stones singer Mick Jagger tweeted: "Chuck you were amazing &amp; your music is engraved inside us forever."</p>
<p>When Richards inducted Berry into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1986, he said: "It's very difficult for me to talk about Chuck Berry because I've lifted every lick he ever played. This is the gentleman who started it all."</p>
<p>His death came five months after Berry announced plans to release his first album of new music in 38 years sometime in 2017 - a collection of mostly original material recorded and produced by Berry, titled "Chuck" and dedicated to his wife of 68 years, Themetta "Toddy" Berry.</p>
<p>Berry's legacy was tarnished by his reputation as a prickly penny-pincher and run-ins with the law, including sex-related offenses after he achieved stardom.</p>
<p>Marking his 90th birthday in 2016 by announcing his new album, Berry listed T-Bone Walker, Carl Hogan of Louis Jordan's band and Charlie Christian from Benny Goodman's band as his guitar influences, but his lyrical style was all his own. Punchy wordplay and youth-oriented subject matter earned him the nickname "the eternal teenager" early in his career.</p>
<h2>KEY COLLABORATOR</h2>
<p>Berry came along at a time when much of the United States remained racially segregated, but it was hard for young audiences of any color to resist a performer who delivered such a powerful beat with so much energy and showmanship.</p>
<p>Berry said he performed his signature bent-knee, head-bobbing "duck walk" across more than 4,000 concert stages. He said he invented the move as a child in order to make his mother laugh as he chased a ball under a table.</p>
<p>Some critics suggested it was his former pianist, Johnnie Johnson, who composed the tunes while Berry only penned the lyrics. Johnson sued Berry in 2000 for song royalties, saying they were equal collaborators on many of the hits, but the case was dismissed on grounds that the statute of limitations had expired.</p>
<p>It was with Johnson that Berry first made his mark, playing at black clubs in the St. Louis area at the musically ripe age of 27. Berry started out filling in with Johnson's group, known as Sir John's Trio, in 1953, and Johnson eventually acknowledged Berry's talent, charisma and business acumen by allowing the group to evolve into the Chuck Berry Trio.</p>
<p>At the suggestion of blues legend Muddy Waters, Berry auditioned for Chess Records, the white-owned Chicago label that put out scores of blues hits. The result was the rockabilly tune "Ida Red," which became a hit after it was retitled "Maybellene" and discovered by white audiences.</p>
<p>When the record came out, Berry said he was stunned to see that pioneering rock 'n' roll disc jockey Alan Freed and another man he had never met, Russ Fratto, were listed as co-writers of "Maybellene." The shared credits deprived him of some royalty payments, but Berry dismissed it at the time as part of the "payola" system that determined which records got radio play in the 1950s. He later regained all the rights to his compositions.</p>
<h2>ONLY ONE NO. 1 HIT</h2>
<p>Berry and Johnson collaborated for some 30 years on such rock anthems as "School Days," "Roll Over Beethoven," "Back in the U.S.A.," "Reelin' and Rockin'," "Rock &amp; Roll Music," "No Particular Place to Go," "Memphis" and "Sweet Little Sixteen." But Berry's only No. 1 hit was "My Ding-a-Ling," a throwaway novelty song that seemed to be a juvenile sex reference.</p>
<p>Berry's reputation for being greedy and grouchy was evident in the 1987 documentary "Hail! Hail! Rock and Roll," which focused on a 60th-birthday concert that Keith Richards organized for him. The movie's makers said Berry refused to show up for filming each day unless given a bag of cash.</p>
<p>"He was an oddly cheap character in some ways," Jagger told Mojo magazine. "He ... was always rude to everyone. He became too much of a parody of himself."</p>
<p>Berry was born Oct. 18, 1926, the third of six children whose father was a contractor and church deacon and whose mother was a schoolteacher. They lived in a relatively prosperous black section of St. Louis known as the Ville.</p>
<p>In the first of his brushes with the law, Berry was sent to a reformatory as a teenager for armed robbery. After his release at age 21, he worked in an auto plant and as a photographer and trained to be a hairdresser.</p>
<p>As he became a star, Berry irked some in St. Louis by acquiring property in a previously white area and opening his own nightclub, where another legal scrape nearly ended his career.</p>
<p>At a show in Texas in 1959, Berry had met a 14-year-old Native American girl and hired her to work at the St. Louis club. She was later fired and then arrested on a prostitution charge, which led to Berry being convicted for violating the Mann Act, transporting a woman across state lines for immoral purposes. He was sent to prison in 1962 for a year and a half and wrote several songs while incarcerated, including "No Particular Place to Go."</p>
<p>Berry had more trouble in 1979 when he was convicted of tax evasion, serving four months in prison, and in the 1990s when a number of women accused him of videotaping them in the bathrooms of his restaurant-club in Wentzville, Missouri.</p>
<p>While the hits did not keep coming for Berry, the tributes never stopped, and he continued playing a monthly show at a St. Louis nightclub into his late 80s. He received a Grammy award for lifetime achievement in 1984 and his 1986 induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame made him part of the inaugural class.</p>
<p>Illustrating his influence, a recording of "Johnny B. Goode" was included in a collection of music sent into space aboard the unmanned 1977 Voyager I probe to provide aliens a taste of Earth culture.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[PPP leader Sharjeel Memon released by NAB after brief detention]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134798-PPP-leader-Sharjeel-Memon-released-by-NAB-after-brief-detention?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sun, 19 Mar 2017 02:23:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134798-PPP-leader-Sharjeel-Memon-released-by-NAB-after-brief-detention?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-19/l_134798_031520_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISLAMABAD: Pakistan Peoples' Party senior leader Sharjeel Memon was released after being briefly detained by the National Accountability Bureau on early Sunday morning from Islamabad airport.</strong></p>
<p>While talking to Geo News after his release, Memon said &nbsp;he will give his point of view on the nearly two and a half hours detention in a press conference today (Sunday) after consulting his lawyers.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Memon spoke to his family members and the chief minister of Sindh after being released.&nbsp;</p>
<p>NAB released the former provincial informational minister after getting verification and undertaking on his bail before arrest from his lawyer, Shakeel Abbasi.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/undertaking.jpeg.jpg" alt="undertaking.jpeg" /></p>
<p>Islamabad High Court has granted bail before arrest to Memon till March 20.</p>
<p>Memon was taken into custody from Islamabad airport by the NAB personnel immediately after his arrival from Dubai. Memon arrived in the country along with the Sindh ministers, Mukesh Chawla, Imdad Pitafi, Fayyaz Ali Butt and Nawab Taimur Talpur.</p>
<p>According to sources privy to the development, six plain-cloth personnel under the deputy director of NAB's crime wing took Memon into their custody from Benazir Bhutto International Airport on the advice of NAB`s Karachi division immediately when he came outside from the flight, EK-614. The provincial legislator was shifted to an undisclosed location. &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Adviser to Sindh CM Nawab Taimur Talpur informed Geo News that Memon resisted his arrest which led to brief manhandling. Talpur added the former minister is scheduled to appear before the court on Monday.</p>
<p>"Chaudhry Nisar`s Gullu Butt ripped apart the copies of legal documents while taking Memon into their custody," Talpur claimed. "Memon was taken away in a disgraceful manner despite him giving his utmost cooperation."&nbsp;</p>
<p>He added the issue has not ended but has now begun.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Sources informed that Memon after his release moved to Sindh House of Islamabad and contacted the chief&nbsp;minister of Sindh.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/Sharjeeeeel.jpg" alt="Sharjeeeeel" /> &nbsp;</p>
<p>NAB has filed a reference against Memon and 10 others in an accountability court of Karachi for alleged corruption of around Rs5.76billion.</p>
<p>Besides Memon, other accused include Zulfiqar Ali Shallwani, Aneeta Baloch, Mansoor Ahmed Rajput, Mohammad Yousuf Kaboro, Inaam Akbar, Altaf Hussain Memon, Riyaz Manir, Fazal Mehmood, Mohammad Hanif, Asim, Masood Hashmi, Gulzar Ali, Suleman Mansoor Umer, Syed Naveed and Sarang Latif Chandio.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Memon was living in a self-imposed exile for more than two years in Dubai and London.</p>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Pre-August 22 MQM suits Sindh govt, says Sattar]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134795-Pre-August-22-MQM-suits-Sindh-govt-says-Sattar?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 23:54:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134795-Pre-August-22-MQM-suits-Sindh-govt-says-Sattar?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134795_115556_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: Muttahida Qaumi Movement-Pakistan chief Farooq Sattar said the MQM which existed before August 22 suits Sindh government.</strong></p>
<p>Addressing the foundation day gathering of the party here, Sattar said the Pakistan People's Party-led government of Sindh supports pre-August MQM. "The incidents of August 22 may help safeguard the policy of looting the downtrodden people."</p>
<p>The MQM since its inception has been marking its foundation day on March 22 every year, but the splitting of the party led the MQM-Pakistan chief Farooq Sattar to designate March 18 as the foundation day.</p>
<p>He alleged that the PPP's interests do not coincide with Pakistan's. Criticizing the provincial government, MQM-Pakistan chief noted that the opposition leader in Sindh Assembly has not been given time for meeting the chief minister for last three months.</p>
<p>The statements came less than 24 hours of Sattar's arrest by Sindh Police. He was whisked to Chakiwara Police Station but later released after brief detention.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Arsenal manager to announce his future plans ‘very soon’]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134793-Arsenal-manager-to-announce-his-future-plans-very-soon?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 23:31:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134793-Arsenal-manager-to-announce-his-future-plans-very-soon?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134793_113200_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>LONDON: Arsene Wenger revealed he will make an announcement about his Arsenal future "very soon" after his side&acute;s problems increased in a 3-1 defeat at West Bromwich Albion on Saturday.</strong><br />"I know what I&acute;ll do in my future, so you will know very soon," Wenger told reporters after Arsenal&acute;s fourth loss in five Premier League games.<br />Wenger, Arsenal&acute;s manager since 1996, is under heavy pressure, after his team was thrashed 10-2 on aggregate by Bayern Munich in the Champions League and fell five points off the top four in the Premier League.<br />Gary Cahill&acute;s 87th-minute winner earned leaders Chelsea a 2-1 win at Stoke City that sent them 13 points clear, while champions Leicester City&acute;s resurgence continued with a 3-2 victory at West Ham United.<br />Craig Dawson scored two headers at The Hawthorns as West Brom condemned Arsenal to a sixth defeat in nine games in all competitions.<br />Dawson&acute;s 12th-minute opener was cancelled out by Alexis Sanchez, but substitute Hal Robson-Kanu restored the hosts&acute; lead before Dawson headed in his second goal with 15 minutes to play.<br />Rival groups of Arsenal fans paid for two planes trailing banners to fly over the ground during the game, one reading "NO CONTRACT #WENGER OUT", the other "IN ARSENE WE TRUST".<br />"You will see," Wenger added on the subject of his future. "Today I do not necessarily worry about that. We are in a unique bad patch we never had in 20 years.<br />"We lose game after game at the moment and that for me is much more important than my future."<br />Arsenal also lost goalkeeper Petr Cech to a muscular problem and Wenger revealed talisman Sanchez had sustained an ankle injury that "doesn&acute;t look good".<br />Chelsea was missing Eden Hazard at Stoke&acute;s Bet365 Stadium due to what manager Antonio Conte termed a "little problem" affecting his calf.<br />They took the lead in the 13th minute when Willian&acute;s free-kick from wide on the left caught out Stoke goalkeeper Lee Grant at his near post.<br />Jonathan Walters levelled with a 38th-minute penalty awarded for a push on him by Cahill, but the England defender atoned to smash in a late winner from Cesc Fabregas&acute;s free-kick.<br />Stoke&acute;s Phil Bardsley was sent off in stoppage time for a second bookable offence.</p>
<p><strong>Lukaku double</strong> </p>
<p>"I am pleased because to play Stoke at this point of the season, you have to be prepared mentally and physically," said Conte.<br />"We have a 10-point gap, 13 at the moment, but I like to think our opponents will win tomorrow. We have to look at ourselves."<br />Chelsea provisionally moved 13 points clear of Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester City ahead of Sunday&acute;s games.<br />Second-place Tottenham host Southampton, while City, level on points with Spurs, entertains Liverpool, who trail Pep Guardiola&acute;s side by a point.<br />A day after being drawn against Atletico Madrid in the Champions League quarter-finals, Leicester won 3-2 at West Ham to record a fourth straight win since Craig Shakespeare succeeded Claudio Ranieri as manager.<br />Leicester led 2-0 inside seven minutes; Riyad Mahrez&acute;s cross from the right curling straight in before Robert Huth headed in a cross from Marc Albrighton.<br />Manuel Lanzini&acute;s 20th-minute free-kick reduced the arrears before Jamie Vardy smashed in Leicester&acute;s third.<br />Despite Andre Ayew reducing the arrears, the visitors held on to pull six points clear of the bottom three.<br />"We showed all the attributes to win a game. We started really well and got the goals, but it was backs to the wall at the end," Shakespeare told the BBC.<br />"We have important league games before the Champions League game with Atletico Madrid. We needed something from today, heading into the international break. We can recharge the batteries now."<br />Everton drew level on points with fifth-place Arsenal, albeit having played two more games, after Romelu Lukaku scored his 20th and 21st goals of the campaign in a 4-0 home win over Hull City.<br />Dominic Calvert-Lewin and Enner Valencia were also on target, while Hull lost Tom Huddlestone to a straight red card for a foul on Idrissa Gueye.<br />Watford captain Troy Deeney&acute;s own goal gifted Crystal Palace a 1-0 win -- their third successive victory -- that elevated Sam Allardyce&acute;s side four points clear of danger.<br />Bottom club Sunderland spurned a valuable opportunity to make up ground in a 0-0 draw at home to Burnley that left them seven points from safety.<br />Palace&acute;s win means Swansea City slipped to fourth-bottom ahead of their trip to Bournemouth in the day&acute;s late game.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[G20 financial leaders row back on free trade pledge]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134792-G20-financial-leaders-row-back-on-free-trade-pledge?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 23:15:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134792-G20-financial-leaders-row-back-on-free-trade-pledge?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134792_111535_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>The world's financial leaders rowed back on a pledge to keep an open and inclusive global trade system after being unable to find a suitable compromise with an increasingly protectionist United States.</strong></p>
<p>Making only a token reference to trade in their communiqu&eacute;, finance ministers and central bank chiefs from the world's top 20 economies broke with a decade-long tradition of endorsing open trade, a clear defeat for host nation Germany, which has fought to maintain the G20's past commitments.</p>
<p>In the new US administration's biggest clash yet with the international community, G20 finance chiefs also rowed back on a pledge to support climate change finance, an anticipated outcome after US President Donald Trump called global warming a "hoax".</p>
<p>"We are working to strengthen the contribution of trade to our economies," G20 finance chiefs said after a two-day meeting in the German resort town of Baden Baden, well short of a past commitment for rules-based, transparent, non-discriminatory, open and inclusive multilateral trade.</p>
<p>Seeking to put "America first", Trump has already pulled out of a key trade agreement and proposed a new tax on imports, arguing that certain trade relationships need to be reworked to make them fairer for US workers.</p>
<p>US Treasury Secretary Steven Mnuchin, who represented the Trump administration in his first G20 meeting, earlier said it had no desire to get into trade wars but trade needed to be made fairer, a reference to big trade deficits with key G20 members, such as Germany and China.</p>
<p>After meeting German Chancellor Angela Merkel on Friday, Trump said he did not believe in isolationism but that trade policy should be fairer.</p>
<p>International trade makes up almost half of global economic output and officials said the issue could be revisited at a meeting of G20 leaders in July.</p>
<p><strong>CLIMATE CHANGE ALSO MISSING</strong></p>
<p>The communiqu&eacute; also dropped a reference, used by the G20 last year, on the readiness to finance measures against climate change as agreed in Paris in 2015, because of opposition from the United States and Saudi Arabia.</p>
<p>Trump has suggested global warming was a "hoax" concocted by China to hurt US industry and vowed to scrap the Paris climate accord aimed at curbing greenhouse gas emissions.</p>
<p>Trump's administration on Thursday proposed a 31 per cent cut to the Environmental Protection Agency's budget as the White House seeks to eliminate climate change programs and trim initiatives to protect air and water quality.</p>
<p>Asked about climate change funding, Mick Mulvaney, Trump's budget director, said on Thursday: "We consider that to be a waste of money."</p>
<p>The G20 did, however, show continuity in its foreign exchange policies, using past phrases on currency markets.</p>
<p>"We reaffirm our previous exchange rate commitments, including that we will refrain from competitive devaluations and we will not target our exchange rates for competitive purposes," the G20 said.</p>
<p>Leaders also upheld their commitments to financial sector regulation, supporting the finaliSation of bank rules known as Basel III, provided they do not significantly raise overall capital requirements.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[KP Assembly speaker rebuts corruption allegations against him]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134791-KP-Assembly-speaker-rebuts-corruption-allegations-against-him?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 23:05:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134791-KP-Assembly-speaker-rebuts-corruption-allegations-against-him?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134791_110558_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISLAMABAD: Speaker of the Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Assembly Asad Qaisar Saturday rebutted corruption allegations against him and asked for proof of his alleged properties.</strong></p>
<p>According to sources, a NAB director, in his letter written to the NAB chief, stated that Qaisar shared a 14-marla house with his four brothers, but now he owns a five-kanal bungalow worth Rs50 million, it emerged on Friday.</p>
<p>The letter read that the KP Assembly speaker has had a house worth Rs350 million built on 35 kanals of land in Bani Gala.</p>
<p>&ldquo;I will gift the bungalow to the person who points to me its exact location,&rdquo; Qaisar remarked sarcastically at a news conference in Islamabad.</p>
<p>The provincial assembly speaker said that he has declared his assets to the election commission as well as in his tax returns. He also claimed to have paid Rs1.1 million tax this year.</p>
<p>Qaisar said that appointments on senior assembly positions were made through National Testing Service (NTS) after placing advertisements. Hiring in Class-4 was done as per quota as laid down in the law, he added.</p>
<p>Condemning what he called &ldquo;propaganda&rdquo;, the speaker said he was being subjected to character assassination.</p>
<p>He said that the National Accountability Bureau (NAB) has not yet contacted him over the allegations.</p>
<p>Meanwhile, Chief Minister KP Pervez Khattak came out in support of the speaker and said that party chairman Imran Khan has full confidence in him.</p>
<p>The NAB official in his letter had said that there have been allegations against Asad Qaisar of receiving 30 per cent kickbacks in different development projects, and that there is a clear difference between the speaker's assets and his sources of income.</p>
<p>The letter further read that Qaisar is also accused of illegally appointing 55 individuals on various provincial assembly jobs and influencing academic results of schools, sources added.</p>
<p>In his response, Speaker Asad Qaisar had said that he purchased land in Bani Gala in 2012, before his party came into power in Khyber Pakhtunkhwa. "All formalities were fulfilled regarding the appointments."</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[US Secret Service laptop with sensitive info on Trump stolen in NY]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134790-US-Secret-Service-laptop-with-sensitive-info-on-Trump-stolen-in-NY?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 22:44:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134790-US-Secret-Service-laptop-with-sensitive-info-on-Trump-stolen-in-NY?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134790_104451_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>A laptop was stolen from a US Secret Service agent in New York and remains missing, the agency said in a statement Friday, amid reports that the device contained floor plans of Trump Tower.</strong></p>
<p>CNN&mdash;citing law enforcement sources in New York&mdash;said that though the computer was highly encrypted, it contained Trump Tower floor plans and other sensitive contents.</p>
<p>US President Donald Trump resided in the luxury high-rise before moving into the White House. His wife Melania and youngest son Barron still live there.</p>
<p>The Secret Service did not detail the contents of the laptop, but emphasised that such devices "contain multiple layers of security including full disk encryption and are not permitted to contain classified information," adding that an investigation is ongoing.</p>
<p>CNN said the laptop was taken from the agent&acute;s car in Brooklyn on Thursday morning.</p>
<p>The elite agency is tasked with protecting the US president, former presidents and vice presidents, as well as foreign heads of state on official visits.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Notorious Hindu hardliner picked by BJP to head India´s biggest state]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134789-Notorious-Hindu-hardliner-picked-by-BJP-to-head-Indias-biggest-state?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 22:28:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134789-Notorious-Hindu-hardliner-picked-by-BJP-to-head-Indias-biggest-state?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134789_102841_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Prime Minister Narendra Modi&acute;s right-wing party Saturday picked a controversial firebrand leader to head India&acute;s most populous state, where it won a landslide victory last week.</strong></p>
<p>Modi&acute;s Hindu nationalist Bharatiya Janata Party won an absolute majority in the northern state of Uttar Pradesh, home to 220 million people and seen as a bellwether of national politics, in a massive vote of confidence for the premier halfway into his first term.</p>
<p>After an hours-long meeting with local BJP legislators on Saturday, senior party leader M. Venkaiah Naidu announced 44-year-old Yogi Adityanath as Uttar Pradesh&acute;s next chief minister.</p>
<p>"Tomorrow Yogi Adityanath will take oath as chief minister," Naidu said at a press conference in Uttar Pradesh&acute;s capital Lucknow late Saturday.</p>
<p>Earlier television footage showed BJP workers garlanding and feeding sweets to the Hindu hardliner who was draped in his iconic saffron-coloured robe.</p>
<p>A five-time MP from the BJP, Adityanath is a popular leader known for his fiery Hindu rhetoric who has stirred controversies over his polarising and inflammatory speeches against Muslims -- who form nearly 20 percent of the state&acute;s population.</p>
<p>Most recently, he lauded US President Trump&acute;s travel ban that aimed to halt immigrants from a handful of Muslim-majority countries from entering America, saying India needed similar action to check terrorism.</p>
<p>He has often fanned flames over religious conversions, inter-religion marriages and has reportedly been arrested and charged with several crimes in the past including rioting, attempt to murder and trespassing on burial places.</p>
<p>The rise of the Hindu priest-turned-politician in Uttar Pradesh, a state prone to sectarian strife, surprised many after Modi made his development agenda the focus of his campaign in the region, which is traditionally fractured along caste and religious lines.</p>
<p>Observers questioned whether Adityanath would continue pushing his "Hindutva", loosely translated as "Hinduness", ideology as chief minister.</p>
<p>"PM @narendramodi says development &amp; growth is his primary agenda. Allowing Hindutva hardliners to helm a major state is a costly mistake," said senior journalist Malini Parthasarathy on Twitter as #YogiAdityanath became a top-trending topic in India.</p>
<p>But the BJP, which won 312 of the total 403 seats in Uttar Pradesh, reassured Adityanath would work for development and anti-corruption.</p>
<p>"This mandate is against caste politics, religious politics," Naidu said.</p>
<p>With last week&acute;s clear win in the politically crucial state, the BJP hopes to boost Modi&acute;s chances for a second term in 2019 general elections but it was unclear whether Adityanath&acute;s appointment would help it get there or backfire.</p>
<p>Modi&acute;s dominance has been largely unchallenged since he won the first overall majority in three decades in 2014 elections on a pledge to wipe out corruption and kickstart the economy.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Siemens says failure to publish company history not a cover-up]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134788-Siemens-says-failure-to-publish-company-history-not-a-cover-up?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 22:19:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134788-Siemens-says-failure-to-publish-company-history-not-a-cover-up?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134788_101926_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>FRANKFURT. Germany industrial and engineering giant Siemens said a decision not to publish a manuscript about the company&acute;s recent history, including some findings about a corruption scandal, did not amount to a cover-up.</strong><br /> German weekly Der Spiegel said Siemens had failed to honour an agreement with two historians to publish a book manuscript which has been completed since 2014. Siemens was involved in one of Germany&acute;s biggest corporate bribery scandals.<br /> The company was exposed as having run an elaborate bribery network, paying more than $1 billion in kickbacks to win contracts worldwide.<br /> In a written statement, Siemens emphatically denied allegations raised in Der Spiegel about potentially withholding relevant information about the bribery scandal.<br /> "The company comprehensively researched the corruption affair 10 years ago, giving authorities and internal investigators full access to relevant information," it said, adding that privacy and corporate confidentiality considerations prohibited a more full disclosure of transcripts from management and supervisory board minutes.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Online counseling lowers blood pressure as much as meds]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134787-Online-counseling-lowers-blood-pressure-as-much-as-meds?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 22:08:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134787-Online-counseling-lowers-blood-pressure-as-much-as-meds?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134787_100933_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>WASHINGTON: People who received regular lifestyle counseling online were able to lower their blood pressure as much as a medication would, researchers said Saturday.</strong><br />Their study involved 264 people with high blood pressure and an average age of 58.<br />The subjects&acute; average blood pressure began at around 140/90 mmHg, meaning they had what is clinically known as stage 1 hypertension.<br />Most were already taking at least one drug to cut their blood pressure. <br />Patients enrolled through the website of the Heart and Stroke Association of Canada and were randomly assigned to either an e-counseling group or a control group.<br />Both groups received emails during the year-long trial, first weekly, then monthly.<br />Those in the e-counseling group were "provided links to online multimedia and interactive tools to increase motivation and skills to begin and sustain a heart-healthy lifestyle," the study said.<br />"These included video clips featuring characters discussing their own high blood pressure diagnosis and efforts to make lifestyle changes, as well as tools for tracking diet and level of physical activity."<br />The control group saw more generic information about heart-healthy living.<br />By the end of the study period, the more engaging online content seemed to have had an effect, and patients in that group reduced their systolic blood pressure -- the higher number in a blood-pressure reading -- by 10 millimeters of mercury (mmHg).<br />That was a statistically significant difference compared to the control group, which saw a 6 mmHg reduction.<br />"The electronic counseling intervention had an effect similar to that of adding an additional blood-pressure-lowering medication," said lead study author Robert Nolan, associate professor at the University of Toronto.<br />"We think this lifestyle counseling intervention can complement and optimize the effectiveness of medical therapy to reduce high blood pressure."<br />The study was released at American College of Cardiology&acute;s annual meeting in Washington.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Pakistanis are terrified of terrorism too: Kalki Koechlin]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134785-Pakistanis-are-terrified-of-terrorism-too-Kalki-Koechlin?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 21:53:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134785-Pakistanis-are-terrified-of-terrorism-too-Kalki-Koechlin?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134785_095347_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Pakistanis are as terrified of terrorism as anyone else in the world, remarked Bollywood actress Kalki Koechlin.</strong></p>
<p>The actress, who has starred in Dev D, was speaking about her experience of shooting a documentary in Pakistan at the India Today Conclave 2017, which is being held in Grand Hyatt in Mumbai.</p>
<p>Speaking about the documentary <em>Azmaish</em>, directed by Pakistani filmmaker Sabiha Sumar, she remarked that she took the project because of her neutrality on the Pakistan-India issue. &nbsp;</p>
<p>Further she stated, &ldquo;From my point of view, I accepted the project out of curiosity. I had never been to Pakistan and I only knew India and Pakistan in terms of conflicts. I wanted to see another aspect, perhaps, a more human aspect,&rdquo; reports <a href="http://indianexpress.com/article/entertainment/bollywood/cant-expect-bollywood-to-stand-up-for-politics-in-india-kalki-koechlin-4573769/">Indian media. </a></p>
<p>Speaking about her experience in Pakistan, Kalki said &ldquo;A lot of things surprised me. One thing that I loved was their curiosity because there&rsquo;s very little outside influence in Pakistan vis-a-vis India. The openness with which they met me was very surprising.&rdquo;</p>
<p>She remarked that the documentary focuses on the everyday struggles of the people on both sides of the border</p>
<p>Cricket and Bollywood are the two things that unite India and Pakistan, she remarked. "Bollywood is huge in Pakistan. People recognised me because of&nbsp;Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani.&nbsp;Even with India, a lot of us are unified because of movies. People of northeast India speak Hindi because of Bollywood.&rdquo;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Hate speech case: Court approves bail plea of MQM's Qamar Mansoor]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134776-Hate-speech-case-Court-approves-bail-plea-of-MQMs-Qamar-Mansoor?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 21:11:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134776-Hate-speech-case-Court-approves-bail-plea-of-MQMs-Qamar-Mansoor?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134776_091112_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: An anti-terrorism court (ATC) on Saturday approved bail plea of Muttahida Qaumi Movement (MQM) leader Qamar Mansoor in a case registered against him for facilitating August 22 inflammatory speech, and ordered his release.</strong></p>
<p>Mansoor was arrested along with fellow Rabita Committee member Kaif-ul-Wara in a pre-dawn raid on the party's Nine Zero headquarters on July 17, last year. He was charged with 'arranging and facilitating' hate speeches.</p>
<p>The inflammatory speech by his party's London-based supremo on August 22, 2016 had stirred unrest in Karachi.</p>
<p>The violence claimed life of a man and left eight others wounded, as charged party workers attacked some media houses and vandalised public property.</p>
<p>The ATC, however, today approved Mansoor's bail plea and ordered his release against security bonds worth Rs4.3 million.</p>
<p>The three cases relating to anti-Pakistan speeches have been transferred to District Malir. SSP Malir Rao Anwar will now be heading investigations of these cases.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Missing Nizamuddin Dargah clerics return to Karachi safe and sound]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134773-Missing-Nizamuddin-Dargah-clerics-return-to-Karachi-safe-and-sound?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 20:45:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134773-Missing-Nizamuddin-Dargah-clerics-return-to-Karachi-safe-and-sound?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134773_084504_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: The two chief clerics of India&rsquo;s Hazrat Nizamuddin Aulia Dargah have safely returned to Karachi, sources told Geo News on Saturday, three days after family members said they had gone missing in Pakistan.</strong></p>
<p>Syed Asif Ali Nizami (Chief Priest) and his nephew Nazim al Nizami arrived Karachi to meet their relatives twelve days ago (March 6, 2017). Both of them were reported to have gone missing on March 14, after which efforts were intensified to locate them.</p>
<p>The two clerics, however, returned to Karachi on Saturday. Sources said that they had gone to visit their followers in interior Sindh, but were unable to get in touch with relatives because of non-availability of cellular services there.</p>
<p>"My father and cousin went missing since March 14. We are really upset. We appeal Pakistani authorities to ensure their early recovery,&rdquo; said Syed Sajid Ali Nizami, son of Syed Asif Ali Nizami on Friday.</p>
<p>In response to the matter, Pakistan Foreign Office said that the issue was being investigated.</p>
<p>"The FO has received Indian MEA's request through Pakistan high commission in New Delhi last evening," said Nafees Zakariya, spokesperson for the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.</p>
<p>"We referred the matter to the concerned quarters and they are actively pursuing it," Zakariya added.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[G20 to jointly fight cyber attacks on bank sector]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134771-G20-to-jointly-fight-cyber-attacks-on-bank-sector?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 20:32:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134771-G20-to-jointly-fight-cyber-attacks-on-bank-sector?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134771_083228_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>The world's biggest economies will pledge to jointly fight cyber attacks on the global banking system, one of the biggest coordinated efforts yet to protect lenders since an $81 million heist of the Bangladesh central bank's account last year.</strong></p>
<p>Meeting in the German resort town of Baden-Baden, G20 finance chiefs will agree to fight attacks regardless of their origin and promise cross-border cooperation to maintain financial stability, according to a draft document seen by Reuters.</p>
<p>"We will promote the resilience of financial services and institutions in G20 jurisdictions against malicious use of information and communication technologies, including from countries outside the G20," it said.</p>
<p>However, it dropped an earlier reference for enhanced security requirements for financial services.</p>
<p>Cyber crime became a top priority after an elaborate heist on the Bangladesh central bank's account at the Federal Reserve Bank of New York last year, an unprecedented theft that exposed the vulnerabilities of the system.</p>
<p>The agreement, set to be finalised on Saturday, will come just days after the United States charged two intelligence agents from Russia, another G20 member, with masterminding the 2014 theft of 500 million Yahoo accounts.</p>
<p>The indictment was the first time US authorities have criminally charged Russian spies for cyber offences including for computer fraud, economic espionage, theft of trade secrets, and wire fraud.</p>
<p>The charges came amid a swirl of controversies relating to alleged Kremlin-backed hacking of the 2016 US presidential election and possible links between Russian figures and associates of US President Donald Trump.</p>
<p>In the banking world, attacks through the global SWIFT bank transfer system have continued to increase with the network recording a "meaningful" number of attacks with about a fifth of them resulting in stolen funds since the Bangladesh heist, the firm said late last year.</p>
<p>In other highly publicised attacks, retailer Tesco Plc's banking arm said 2.5 million pounds ($3 million) had been stolen from 9,000 customers last year while hackers also stole more than 2 billion rubles ($34 million) from correspondent accounts at the Russian central bank and from accounts in commercial banks.</p>
<p>The European Union is considering testing banks' defences against cyber attacks with concerns growing about the industry's vulnerability to hacking.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[China creates world's first coal-to-ethanol production line]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134770-China-creates-worlds-first-coal-to-ethanol-production-line?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 20:15:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134770-China-creates-worlds-first-coal-to-ethanol-production-line?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134770_081713_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>China has successfully created the world's first production line to turn coal into ethanol, or drinking alcohol, the Chinese Academy of Sciences said on Saturday.</strong></p>
<p>Created by Shaanxi Yanchang Petroleum and the academy's Dalian Institute of Chemical Physics in Liaoning province, the production line went into operation in January and has the capacity to make more than 100,000 metric tons of pure ethanol every year, according to Liu Zhongmin, the institute's deputy director.</p>
<p>By 2020, China would build a factory capable of producing one million tons of ethanol each year using the same technology, he added.</p>
<p>The country currently produces seven million tons of ethanol each year using other methods, which can "hardly satisfy" its industrial and energy needs, according to Liu.</p>
<p>"Most countries produce ethanol using food, such as corn or sugar cane, but this is not a viable option for China given its massive population," he said.</p>
<p>"By turning China's abundant coal resources into ethanol, the technology will help safeguard our energy and food security.</p>
<p>"Moreover, ethanol is a green fuel and versatile ingredient.</p>
<p>"Utilising it could reduce our dependency on fossil fuels, and make our industrial production and energy structure more environmental friendly," Liu said.</p>
<p>In addition to alcoholic beverages, ethanol can be used to produce thousands of everyday products from plastics to detergents.</p>
<p>It can also replace more toxic ingredients, such as methanol, during industrial production.</p>
<p>Other uses include mixing it with petroleum to increase its fuel efficiency and reduce pollution.</p>
<p>An abundant supply of ethanol would also make ethanol-fueled vehicles more viable, Liu said.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Radd-ul-Fasaad: 35 suspects arrested in operations across country]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134768-Radd-ul-Fasaad-35-suspects-arrested-in-operations-across-country?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 20:09:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134768-Radd-ul-Fasaad-35-suspects-arrested-in-operations-across-country?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134768_081005_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Around 35 suspects have been apprehended across the country in the last 24 hours, as Operation Radd-ul-Fasaad continues in full swing.</strong></p>
<p>According to Inter-Services Public Relations&nbsp;(ISPR), around six intelligence based operations (IBOs) and 35 cordon and search operations were conducted across the country.</p>
<p>Moreover, joint search and intelligence based operations were conducted by Punjab Rangers, police and intelligence agencies in Punjab.</p>
<p>Fourteen suspects including one Afghan national and one 1 Baloch sub nationalist worker were held during operations in DG Khan, Rawalpindi, Islamabad and Attock.</p>
<p>Weapons, ammunition, currency and foreign passports were also recovered from the suspects&rsquo; possession.</p>
<p>Operation Radd-ul-Fasaad was launched on February 22, after series back-to-back terrorist attacks in the country, in which more than 100 people lost their lives.</p>
<p>The operation includes a broad-spectrum security, counter-terrorism operations in Punjab, and continuation of ongoing operations across&nbsp;the country.</p>
<p>According&nbsp;to the Director-General of the Inter-Services Public Relations (ISPR) wing of the Pakistan Army, the operation aims include the elimination of the residual and latent threat of terrorism, consolidating gains of operations made so far and ensuring the security of Pakistan&rsquo;s borders.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Woman martyred in unprovoked Indian firing across LoC]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134764-Woman-martyred-in-unprovoked-Indian-firing-across-LoC?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 20:03:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134764-Woman-martyred-in-unprovoked-Indian-firing-across-LoC?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134764_070837_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>RAWALPINDI: Indian forces on Saturday resorted to unprovoked firing across the Line of Control, resulting in martyrdom of an elderly woman, the Inter Services Public Relations said in a statement.</strong></p>
<p>Indian border forces violated the ceasefire and targeted civilian population in Kot Kehtera sector along the LoC. The unprovoked fire resulted in martyrdom of a 60-year-old woman in village Thandi Kassi, the statement read.</p>
<p>Pakistani troops, however, gave a befitting response to the unprovoked fire and silenced the enemy guns, it added.</p>
<p>This is the third ceasefire violation by the Indian forces in less than 10 days.</p>
<p>On March 12, two Pakistan citizens were wounded in the cross-border firing by Indian troops in Chirikot sector. The wounded included an elderly man and 15-year-old girl, who were evacuated and shifted to Civil Hospital Abbaspur.</p>
<p>Prior to that a woman was injured due to unprovoked firing by Indian troops in Baroh area of Bhimber sector.</p>
<p>On February 7, a 25-year-old labourer named Ashfaq was injured because of Indian firing in Khuiratta sector; however, he later succumbed to his injuries.</p>
<p>Last year, tensions soared high between the two nuclear-armed adversaries over occupied Kashmir and an attack on Indian army's brigade headquarters in Uri, which left 19 soldiers dead.</p>
<p>This followed frequent flare-ups along the border, but frequency of skirmishes reduced toward the end of the last year.</p>
<p>However, this fresh spate of ceasefire violations indicates that neighbouring country has once again been overcome by its war mania.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Paris police say airport attacker was 'radicalised']]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134748-Man-shot-dead-at-Paris-Orly-airport-after-taking-soldiers-gun-official?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 19:51:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134748-Man-shot-dead-at-Paris-Orly-airport-after-taking-soldiers-gun-official?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134748_075651_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>PARIS: A man who had been investigated for being radicalised was shot dead at Orly airport south of Paris on Saturday after attacking a soldier on patrol and trying to grab her rifle.</strong></p>
<p>The same man is suspected of having shot at police earlier in the day, leaving an officer with minor wounds after being pulled over while driving in a suburb north of the French capital.</p>
<p><strong>Who was the attacker?</strong></p>
<p>Police sources say he is a 39-year-old Frenchman with several previous convictions, including for drugs and armed robbery, who was being sought by police.</p>
<p>His home was searched in 2015 after he was "detected as having been radicalised" but no incriminating evidence was found, the sources said.</p>
<p>French Interior Minister Bruno Le Roux confirmed he was "known to the police and the intelligence services".</p>
<p>The man&acute;s father and brother were being questioned by police Saturday.</p>
<p>Police also searched his house in the northeastern Paris suburb of Garges-les-Gonesse, in the multi-ethnic Seine-Saint-Denis area.</p>
<p>&nbsp;<strong>What happened?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>The suspect was pulled over by police at around 6:55am (0555 GMT) Saturday while driving in Garges-les-Gonesse. He drew a gun and fired shots at the officers, slightly injuring one in the head, before fleeing.</p>
<p>He then continued south to steal another car in the suburb of Vitry-sur-Seine about 10 kilometres (six miles) from Orly airport. In Vitry, he also "burst into a bar and threatened those present," Le Roux said.</p>
<p>Minutes later, at around 8:30am (0730 GMT), he walked onto the departures floor of Orly-Sud terminal, where he tried to grab the rifle of a female officer on patrol with two others.</p>
<p>A senior military source said he knocked the soldier to the ground and grabbed her rifle. The two other soldiers then opened fire, killing him, the source said. Le Roux was adamant that he "did not succeed" in taking the rifle.</p>
<p>No-one else was injured in the melee.</p>
<p>Identity documents found on the attacker matched those presented by the man who fired at police in Garges-les-Gonesse.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Was this a foiled terror attack?&nbsp;</strong></p>
<p>The investigation has been entrusted to anti-terror prosecutors, meaning that authorities suspect terrorism as a possible motive.</p>
<p>France is still under a state of emergency after a series of terror attacks, including the November 2015 massacre in Paris which killed 130 and a truck attack in Nice in July last year which left 86 dead.</p>
<p>The security forces have been repeatedly targeted by Muslim terrorists.</p>
<p>In mid-February, a machete-wielding Egyptian attacked soldiers on patrol outside the Louvre museum in Paris, slightly injuring one of them, before being shot and wounded.</p>
<p>In June 2016 a man claiming allegiance to Daesh stabbed a police couple to death at their home near Paris.</p>
<p>Soldiers have also been targeted in a number of smaller knife attacks.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><strong>Was air travel disrupted?</strong></p>
<p>All flights in and out of Orly airport were suspended Saturday morning. Many inbound flights were diverted to the bigger Charles de Gaulle airport to the north of Paris.</p>
<p>Around 3,000 passengers were evacuated from Orly-Sud terminal, where the attack took place, while elite police teams secured it and swept it for possible explosives. Those at the nearby Orly-Ouest terminal were confined to the building.</p>
<p>By early afternoon Orly-Ouest had reopened and flights were starting to resume.</p>
<p>Orly-Sud had reopened to incoming flights but outgoing flights were still suspended.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[US, China to cooperate on 'dangerous' N.Korea situation]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134766-US-China-to-cooperate-on-dangerous-NKorea-situation?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 19:38:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134766-US-China-to-cooperate-on-dangerous-NKorea-situation?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134766_073834_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>The US and China pledged on Saturday to work together in addressing the threat posed by North Korea's nuclear programme, as US Secretary of State Rex Tillerson warned the situation had reached a &ldquo;dangerous level.&rdquo;</strong></p>
<p>The language from Tillerson and his Chinese counterpart after talks in Beijing was notably conciliatory after a run-up in which US President Donald Trump accused China of doing nothing to control its rogue neighbour while Beijing blamed Washington for fuelling hostilities.</p>
<p>&ldquo;I think we share a common view and a sense that tensions in the peninsula are quite high right now and that things have reached a rather dangerous level,&rdquo; Tillerson said after talks with Chinese Foreign Minister Wang Yi.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We will work together to see if we cannot bring the government in Pyongyang to a place where they want to make a different course, make a course correction, and move away from the development of nuclear weapons,&rdquo; Yi added.</p>
<p>Tillerson arrived in Beijing earlier Saturday after visits to US allies Japan and South Korea where he said the US would no longer observe the &ldquo;failed&rdquo; approach of patient diplomacy favoured by Beijing and followed by the Obama administration.</p>
<p>Trump upped the pressure in a Friday Twitter blast accusing Beijing of failing to use its leverage as North Korea's key diplomatic and trade partner.</p>
<p>&ldquo;North Korea is behaving very badly. They have been 'playing' the United States for years. China has done little to help!&rdquo; Trump said.</p>
<p>The tougher US talk followed two North Korean nuclear tests last year and recent missile launches, including a salvo earlier this month that Pyongyang described as practice for an attack on US bases in Japan.</p>
<p>Beijing is deeply reluctant to put harsh pressure on the unpredictable North lest it trigger a confrontation or a messy regime collapse.</p>
<p>China has hit back at the US, angrily accusing it of escalating the situation by holding military exercises with its ally Seoul and deploying an anti-missile system in South Korea.</p>
<p>Beijing has been calling for a resumption of diplomatic negotiations with North Korea on dismantling its nuclear programme ─ which UN resolutions bar it from pursuing ─ a track pursued for years in the past but which notably failed.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We can either let the situation aggravate and lead to conflict or go back to the right track of negotiations,&rdquo; Wang said.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We both hope to find ways to restart talks and do not give up hope for peace.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Neither side indicated any next steps.<br />Tillerson, a former Exxon oil executive who until this week had adopted a low profile in office, said in Seoul on Friday that the US and its allies were &ldquo;exploring a new range of diplomatic, security, economic measures.&rdquo; He gave no details but said US military action against North Korea remained &ldquo;on the table&rdquo; if Pyongyang escalated its provocations.</p>
<p>China has taken shots at his get-tough approach, saying in recent days that its call for diplomatic talks was the &ldquo;only feasible option&rdquo; and challenging the Trump administration to propose something better. One reason for the amicable tone on Saturday may be that delicate negotiations are ongoing for President Xi Jinping to visit Trump ─ a frequent China critic ─ in a first summit between the leaders next month in the United States.</p>
<p>Tillerson was expected to meet Xi on Sunday morning.</p>
<p>Beijing shares US concerns over Pyongyang's nuclearisation but is careful not to provoke North Korea. But China took one of its toughest steps yet in February, announcing it would halt all imports of North Korean coal ─ a key source of income for the impoverished state ─ for the rest of this year, citing the UN sanctions.</p>
<p>The United Nations has imposed multiple sets of sanctions but China is accused of not fully enforcing them.</p>
<p>Under the Obama administration, the US ruled out diplomatic engagement until Pyongyang made a tangible commitment to denuclearisation, hoping that internal stresses in the isolated country would bring change.</p>
<p>North Korea says it needs to be able to defend itself, and conducted its first underground atomic test in 2006, triggering global condemnation. Four more test blasts have followed.</p>
<p>Beijing also is upset over the US deployment of an anti-missile system to South Korea that Washington and Seoul insist is purely a defensive measure against a possible North Korean attack.</p>
<p>But Beijing says the system undermines its own security and has reacted angrily, imposing a series of measures seen in South Korea as economic retaliation.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[MQM-Pakistan marks 33rd Foundation Day today]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134761-MQM-Pakistan-marks-33rd-Foundation-Day-today?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 18:22:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134761-MQM-Pakistan-marks-33rd-Foundation-Day-today?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134761_062249_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: The Muttahida Qaumi Movement-Pakistan will celebrate its 33rd foundation day in Karachi on Saturday, the first time after having parted ways from its London-based leadership.</strong></p>
<p>The foundation day celebrations, which marks the party&rsquo;s inception in March 1984, will kick off at party&rsquo;s temporary headquarters in PIB Colony this evening.</p>
<p>The MQM since its inception has been marking its foundation day on March 22 every year, but the splitting of the party has led the MQM-Pakistan chief Farooq Sattar to designate March 18 as the foundation day.</p>
<p>In an extraordinary turn of events, MQM leaders in the country distanced themselves from the London-based party chief following an inflammatory speech by him on August 22, 2016 and ensuing violence in Karachi.</p>
<p>The violence claimed life of a man and left eight others wounded, as charged party workers attacked some media houses and vandalised public property.</p>
<p>Sattar, flanked by senior leaders of the party, announced at a press conference in Karachi that future party decisions would be made by party officials in Pakistan.</p>
<p>According to MQM-Pakistan leaders, designating a different day was to ensure the party remains committed to its pledge to work for the betterment of middle-class and the downtrodden people.</p>
<p>Late on Friday night, Sattar was taken into custody when he was returning home after attending a wedding ceremony at the Pakistan Air Force (PAF) Museum in Karachi.</p>
<p>He was whisked to Chakiwara Police Station but later released after brief detention.</p>
<p>Police officials said personnel from the City Division had arrested the MQM-Pakistan leader in a case over hate speech, sedition, and incidents of violence in Karachi on August 22 last year.</p>
<p>Police sources told Geo News that non-bailable arrest warrants had already been issued for Sattar.</p>
<p>.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Turkey starts building ´world´s longest suspension bridge´]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134759-Turkey-starts-building-worlds-longest-suspension-bridge?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 17:47:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134759-Turkey-starts-building-worlds-longest-suspension-bridge?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134759_054900_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>ISTANBUL: Turkey on Saturday started work on building what it says will be the world&acute;s longest suspension bridge, spanning the Dardanelles strait that divides Europe and Asia</strong>.<br /> The bridge is the latest in a succession of massively ambitious infrastructure projects championed by President Recep Tayyip Erdogan and the launch of the project comes a month ahead of a referendum on expanding his powers.<br /> Authorities expect that work on the bridge will be completed in 2023, the year that Turkey celebrates the 100th anniversary of the foundation of the modern republic by Mustafa Kemal Ataturk.<br /> Appropriately, the span of the bridge is to be 2,023 metres (6,637 feet).<br /> This will make it the longest suspension bridge in the world, overtaking the Akashi Kaikyo Bridge in Japan which is just under 2,000 metres long, state media said.<br /> The ground breaking ceremony was attended by Erdogan on the Asian side and Prime Minister Binali Yildirim on the European side of the site.<br /> "The bridge will be the number one in the world. It will connect Europe and Asia," said Erdogan.&nbsp;<br /> The bridge is being built by a four way consortium of Turkish firms Limak and Yapi Merkezi and Daelim and SK of South Korea.<br /> The ceremony was attended by South Korean Minister of Infrastructure and Transport Ho-in Kang.<br /> The bridge will also be the first ever permanent structure to span the Dardanelles -- known as the Hellespont in the ancient world -- which occupy a near mythical place in world history.<br /> Persian king Xerxes is said by the ancient Greek historian Herodotus to have build pontoon bridges across the Hellespont to transport his troops from Asia into Thrace in a campaign of 480 BC.<br /> British romantic poet Lord Byron famously swam across the Hellespont in 1810, a feat repeated by ambitious modern-day swimmers in an annual race.<br /> The area is hugely important to Turks as where Ottoman forces resisted a 1915 invasion by British, Australian and other Allied forces in World War I, known in the West as the Gallipoli campaign.<br /> The resistance of the Ottoman forces is seen as their greatest hour in a war the declining empire lost, and is commemorated with increasing fervour in modern Turkey.<br /> In recognition of this, the bridge will be known as the Canakkale 1915 bridge after the year and the Turkish province where it is located.<br /> Over the last year, Erdogan has opened the first road tunnel underneath the Bosphorus and the third bridge across the Istanbul strait.<br /> </p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Bahria Town’s cleanliness drive continues in Karachi]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134758-Bahria-Towns-cleanliness-drive-continues-in-Karachi?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 17:28:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134758-Bahria-Towns-cleanliness-drive-continues-in-Karachi?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134758_052819_updates.JPG"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: Bahria Town authorities&rsquo; cleanliness drive continued in city&rsquo;s Central District on its sixth day.</strong></p>
<p>The cleaning vehicles picked up trash from Rashid Minhas Road on Saturday.</p>
<p>The drive, which was launched on Monday, seeks to assist in the garbage disposal crisis surrounding the metropolis.</p>
<p>As many as 50 vehicles and 600 personnel for picking up garbage from Karachi&rsquo;s streets have been deployed for the purpose.</p>
<p>According to the plan, the vehicles and volunteers cleaned up Shahrah-e-Pakistan in the first phase of the drive. The other areas which were to be cleaned include Shahrah-e-Noor Jahan, Sher Shah Suri Road and other roads and streets of Karachi, according to the Bahria Town management.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Making a comeback not easy for any cricketer: Hafeez]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134754-Making-a-comeback-not-easy-for-any-cricketer-Hafeez?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 15:48:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134754-Making-a-comeback-not-easy-for-any-cricketer-Hafeez?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134754_034925_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>LAHORE: Former Pakistan captain Muhammad Hafeez said that the time period after his injury was difficult for him.</strong></p>
<p>&ldquo;When I was injured in England I refused to play in the team. After my knee injury healed I got back in the team,&rdquo; he said, adding that making a comeback is not easy for any cricketer.</p>
<p>The batsman admitted that his performance in the Pakistan Super League was not satisfactory, however he said he was satisfied by his performance in Australia.</p>
<p>He said that in the PSL he struggled with his batting initially and twice was knocked out on zero.</p>
<p>He said that for the West Indies series the selectors expressed faith in him and he hoped that he performs well.</p>
<p>Hafeez said that he wanted to play for Pakistan honourably, and any cricketer who brings dishonour to the country should not be forgiven. "It is unfortunate that the team has found itself in the middle of a scandal once again."</p>
<p>Hafeez had sustained a bad case of knee injury during World T20 in March 2016&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>He had returned to cricket some months later but had got injured again halfway through Pakistan tour to England in summer of 2016&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>He had also been suspended from bowling in July 2015 after his action was reported. But his bowling action was cleared in November 2016 and he was allowed to bowl again.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Clear breach of faith in US-Pakistan partnership: Asif Zardari]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134749-Clear-breach-of-faith-in-US-Pakistan-partnership-Asif-Zardari?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 14:23:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134749-Clear-breach-of-faith-in-US-Pakistan-partnership-Asif-Zardari?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134749_023254_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p>&ldquo;Our citizens, just like yours [United States], are peace-loving people, seeking nothing more than stability, freedom and hope for our children,&rdquo; wrote Asif Ali Zardari in a guest post for Forbes.com.</p>
<p>The former president and husband of Benazir Bhutto discussed the role of billions of dollars invested by the United States in Pakistan over the course of fifteen years noted that the high price of &ldquo;this investment&rdquo; brought greater stability in the country and reduced threat from extremists, however, the &ldquo;well of goodwill from which we [Pakistan] can draw is not endless.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Zardari emphasised that Pakistan, which he believes remains a potential flashpoint for South Asia and the world, should carry more of its own weight while increasing military and commercial cooperation with its allies. &nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;The terrorists who attack our people here are the same who attack Americans and other innocents abroad,&rdquo; he wrote, elaborating on how the US should continue to be Pakistan&rsquo;s partner. He reasoned how the US war on terror is not just drawn from goodwill but the country&rsquo;s self-interest to eliminate ideas that it disagrees with.</p>
<p>The Pakistani politician said that the democratic values and transparency under Nawaz Sharif&rsquo;s rule has &ldquo;back-slid&rdquo; but the foundations built during his tenure as president yielded tangible results including but not limited to rooting out extremists&rsquo; safe havens, dismantling Al-Qaeda&rsquo;s networks in the region, and seizing nearly 200 tons of improvised explosive device precursors. &ldquo;These successes come at no small price. Pakistan has lost over 60,000 people, both civilian and military, as a direct result of offensives against terrorist networks.&rdquo; He further stated that Pakistan has incurred over $60 billion in economic costs in the war on terror, and the cost only continues to spiral up with passing time.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Sadly, many in Congress fail to recognise these hard-won victories, cutting off hundreds of millions of dollars in reimbursements to Pakistan under the Coalition Support Fund (CSF), a US program for costs incurred in supporting counter-terrorist operations,&rdquo; Zardari wrote. The former president said the entire effort of combing out the region seems to be going to waste as terrorists continue to slip over the borders, evident from recent incidents of terrorism in Afghanistan.</p>
<p>Discussing the US&rsquo; role in building Pakistan economy, home to the world&rsquo;s second-fastest-growing stock exchange, Zardari noted that stability has been restored in the country&rsquo;s economy after nearly half a decade of growth. He expressed hope that the US will continue to nurture Pakistan&rsquo;s economy, which he believes is &ldquo;poised for an even greater advancement in 2017.&rdquo;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Apple likely get rid of thousands of apps with new update]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134742-Apple-likely-get-rid-of-thousands-of-apps-with-new-update?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 13:24:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134742-Apple-likely-get-rid-of-thousands-of-apps-with-new-update?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134742_012414_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Thousands of apps are likely to be killed when the next version of the iOS is rolled out.</strong></p>
<p>New warnings issued with the iOS beta in a dedicated settings menu say that outdated apps &ldquo;"will not work with future versions of iOS."</p>
<p>A new settings menu called &ldquo;app compatibility&rdquo; in the latest public beta for iOS 10.3 specifically lists any outdated apps installed on your device.</p>
<p>An additional warning in the new &ldquo;app compatibility&rdquo; menu shows if a newer version of the app is available. It requests users to &ldquo;contact the app developer for more information," if &ldquo;no update is available.&rdquo;</p>
<p><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/APPLE.jpg" alt="" width="740" height="803" /></p>
<p>Apple plans to force developers to update legacy apps that were created before the 64-bit processors introduced with the iPhone 5S in 2013. The warnings seem to be part of the company&rsquo;s plan to get legacy apps updated.</p>
<p>In the past, the company issued warnings that outdated apps may &ldquo;slow down&rdquo; users&rsquo; phones, in an attempt to shame lazy developers.</p>
<p>This time around, Apple&rsquo;s push to nudge these developers seems to be on an altogether different level of aggression.</p>
<p>Despite placing the requirement of new apps and updates to support 64-bit processors since 2015, at least 187,000 apps still don&rsquo;t support the modern chipset, according to app analytics firm Sensor Tower.</p>
<p>Apple already removed 47,000 apps that failed to meet the set criteria last fall.</p>
<p>While the company has not yet commented on the matter, it seems highly likely that iOS 11 will do away with a significant number of apps.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Foreign airline plane makes emergency landing in Lahore after on board brawl]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134741-Foreign-airline-plane-makes-emergency-landing-in-Lahore-after-on-board-brawl?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 13:17:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134741-Foreign-airline-plane-makes-emergency-landing-in-Lahore-after-on-board-brawl?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134741_012213_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>LAHORE: A brawl on board an Ethiopian Airlines plane led to an emergency landing at the Allama Iqbal International Airport on Saturday. <br /></strong></p>
<p>The plane was en route from Addis Ababa to Beijing when the pilot requested an emergency landing after a fight broke out between a passenger and his medical attendant, both of whom are Chinese nationals.</p>
<p>According to details, a mentally ill patient attacked and injured his attendant during the flight. The attendant was provided medical care at the airport. The medically ill patient and his attendant have both been given permission by the Chinese Consulate to stay in Pakistan and receive treatment.&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Internet goes wild over BBC kid’s I-don’t-care attitude]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134746-Internet-goes-wild-over-BBC-kids-I-dont-care-attitude?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 12:51:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134746-Internet-goes-wild-over-BBC-kids-I-dont-care-attitude?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134746_013922_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>They say &lsquo;fame brings tantrums&rsquo; but with BBC star kid Marion Kelly, things are quite different.</strong></p>
<p>Marion Kelly, the girl who broke into her professor dad&rsquo;s home office in a &lsquo;Hippity-Hoppity&rsquo; mood during a live interview with the BBC has become a star and she couldn&rsquo;t care less about it.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/gallery-1489677036-marionkelly2.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="300" /></p>
<p>Marion has become an internet hit after she showed up at a press conference with her parents in I-don&rsquo;t-give-a-damn attitude.</p>
<p>Marion who appeared at the press conference in a Burberry coat, snazzy glasses with a lollypop, showed everyone that she doesn&rsquo;t care about her fame but rather wants to have the lollipop in peace. (That&rsquo;s the attitude girl)</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/C7BoHjVWkAANOl6.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="301" /></p>
<p>The internet instantly went crazy over Marion Kelly who stole the limelight during the press conference even while doing nothing and being herself. Hundreds of memes have been shared on the internet in which some were calling her a badass fashionista, some were found drooling over her stylish appearance with adorable attitude and wait... That's not it. People are even demanding for President Marion in the future. (woah)</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-20106" src="http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/oboy.gif" alt="Ryan Gosling Approves" width="314" height="314" /></p>
<p>Have a look.</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="de">Zeitgeist ✅ <a href="https://t.co/P4plgjMNzJ">pic.twitter.com/P4plgjMNzJ</a></p>
&mdash; Rachel Waterman (@RW_HofV) <a href="https://twitter.com/RW_HofV/status/842799610586415104">March 17, 2017</a></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">Citizens of Earth. Bow to your new overlord. <a href="https://t.co/ZGHbO2znvA">pic.twitter.com/ZGHbO2znvA</a></p>
&mdash; Adam Johnson (@xtra_shiny) <a href="https://twitter.com/xtra_shiny/status/842159743862947848">March 15, 2017</a></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">do not try to stop them <a href="https://t.co/uKbsjjBdiP">pic.twitter.com/uKbsjjBdiP</a></p>
&mdash; ᴘᴀᴘᴇʀʙᴇᴀᴛssᴄɪssᴏʀs! (@paperbeatstweet) <a href="https://twitter.com/paperbeatstweet/status/841773681659469824">March 14, 2017</a></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">If she isn't President of Earth by the time I'm 80, I'll be bitterly disappointed. <a href="https://t.co/f5qEfaaPT7">pic.twitter.com/f5qEfaaPT7</a></p>
&mdash; David Llewellyn (@TheDaiLlew) <a href="https://twitter.com/TheDaiLlew/status/842049231317794816">March 15, 2017</a></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">I love everything about Marion who interrupted her dad's BBC interview. Love her trench coat and I love her glasses. <a href="https://t.co/U3KLF1LIvF">pic.twitter.com/U3KLF1LIvF</a></p>
&mdash; Yashar (@yashar) <a href="https://twitter.com/yashar/status/842081082019332096">March 15, 2017</a></blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-lang="en">
<p dir="ltr" lang="en">When you know you're BBC interview kid and don't have to even try anymore. <a href="https://t.co/fIcmpZCFlt">pic.twitter.com/fIcmpZCFlt</a></p>
&mdash; Rachel Waterman (@RW_HofV) <a href="https://twitter.com/RW_HofV/status/842287618440237056">March 16, 2017</a>&nbsp;</blockquote>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;Because Marion Kelly has her own swag.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/_95172835_32c79dd0-1556-43ad-ae56-7bdb91d6d0ce-840x473.jpg" alt="" width="600" height="338" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[PSL spot-fixing: Shahzaib says he did not provoke any cricketer]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134736-Shahzaib-Hasan-decides-to-approach-tribunal-in-spot-fixing-case?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 12:49:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134736-Shahzaib-Hasan-decides-to-approach-tribunal-in-spot-fixing-case?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134736_125219_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>LAHORE: &nbsp;Shahzaib Hasan has decided to approach a tribunal after being formally charged by the Pakistan Cricket Board (PCB) in relation to the Pakistan Super League (PSL) spot-fixing scandal.</strong></p>
<p>According to sources, Shahzaib has prepared a legal reply to allegations levelled against him by the PCB. In the reply, Shahzaib states that he did not provoke any player and informed the PCB of everything he knew. The cricketer adds that he is willing to help the PCB in relation to the case.</p>
<p>Sources further add that Shahzaib&rsquo;s written reply will be submitted to the PCB in the next 1-2 days.</p>
<p>On Friday, Shazaib who represented the Karachi Kings in the second edition of the PSL was handed a notice of charges for violating the PCB&rsquo;s anti-corruption code. He has been charged with violations of Code Articles 2.1.4, 2.4.4 and 2.4.5 and has been suspended from participating in all forms of cricket with immediate effect. After being charged, the batsman has 14 days to respond.</p>
<p>Article 2.1.4 of the PCB&rsquo;s anti-corruption code states: &ldquo;Directly or indirectly soliciting, inducing, enticing, instructing, persuading, encouraging or intentionally facilitating any Participant to breach any of the foregoing provisions of this Article 2.1.&rdquo;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Article 2.4.4 reads: &ldquo;Failing to disclose to the PCB Vigilance and Security Department (without unnecessary delay) full details of any approaches or invitations received by the Participant to engage in Corrupt Conduct under this Anti-Corruption Code.&rdquo;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p>Article 2.4.5 states: &ldquo;Failing or refusing to disclose to the PCB Vigilance and Security Department (without unnecessary delay) full details of any incident, fact, or matter that comes to the attention of a Participant that may evidence Corrupt Conduct under this Anti-Corruption Code by another Participant, including (without limitation) approaches or invitations that have been received by another Participant to engage in conduct that would amount to a breach of this Anti-Corruption Code.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Sharjeel, Khalid Latif and Shahzaib can face punishment up to five years, according to the PCB. Mohammad Irfan can face a ban of up to six months.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Pakistani couple gifts $15 million to the University of Notre Dame]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134726-Pakistani-couple-gifts-15-million-to-the-University-of-Notre-Dame?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 12:11:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134726-Pakistani-couple-gifts-15-million-to-the-University-of-Notre-Dame?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134726_122010_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>A Muslim couple hailing from Pakistan announced a $15 million gift to the University of Notre Dame, one of the top Catholic universities, <span style="color: #3366ff;"><a style="color: #3366ff;" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/03/17/your-money/norte-dame-muslim-philanthropists.html?_r=0">The New York Times</a> </span>reported on Friday.</strong></p>
<p>Rafat and Zoreen Ansari, who have spent over 40 years working as medical doctors and raising their children, have earned a reputation as civic leaders in South Bend, Indiana.</p>
<p>Their donation will create the Rafat and Zoreen Ansari Institute for Global Engagement With Religion at University of Notre Dame. The institute will work on deepening knowledge of religion and spread awareness about the traditions and practices of various religions.</p>
<p>&ldquo;We came as immigrants, and this country has given us so much,&rdquo; Mrs. Ansari said in an interview ahead of the announcement. &ldquo;We want to give something back to America, but also to humanity. We want to promote the idea of equality.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The generous gift was a well thought out decision by the couple. &ldquo;We&rsquo;re not billionaires,&rdquo; Mrs. Ansari, who practices family medicine, said while speaking to New York Times. &ldquo;We had to think, how is it going to affect us? There were a lot of parts.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The two doctors, whose youngest child is autistic, have spent thousands of hours and donated over $1 million to nonprofit organizations associated with autism in children.</p>
<p>The couple and their children, who identify as Muslims, began working on a larger gift a year and half ago, when they decided to fund something that would foster a better understanding of religion, including Islam, Judaism, and Christianity. The family, which believes&nbsp; that all religions should be treated with equal respect, aims at fostering religious harmony through a better understanding of religious beliefs.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Some of this money is our children&rsquo;s money,&rdquo; Mr. Ansari said. &ldquo;It would have gone to them. But they came to realize this is a legacy for us,&rdquo; he added while discussing the future inheritance of their three children who were involved in the discussions and planning of the gift.</p>
<p>The gift comes in at a politically charged time when the US and Europe are reconsidering immigration laws for the Muslim community. The gift, which is 18 months in the making, was not extended to make a political statement according to the couple and the university. However, both parties acknowledged that the timing of the announcement could lead people to assign political motivation as a possible reason.</p>
<p>&nbsp;&ldquo;In the last couple of years, the majority of problems have been created by the misunderstandings among the religions,&rdquo; said Mr. Ansari, an oncologist and hematologist. &ldquo;Is this the right time for the announcement? Yes, because there is so much going on.&rdquo;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[Shah Rukh Khan opens up about his meeting with Amir Khan]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134722-Shah-Rukh-Khan-opens-up-about-his-meeting-with-Amir-Khan?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 11:05:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134722-Shah-Rukh-Khan-opens-up-about-his-meeting-with-Amir-Khan?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134722_112515_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>Superstars Shah Rukh Khan and&nbsp;Aamir Khan recently met and their meeting sparked speculations on the internet.</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/Amir-Khan-And-Sharu-Khan-Selfie-Together-678x381.jpg" alt="" width="334" height="378" /></strong></p>
<p>In the past, SRK and Amir Khan were neither seen together in public nor spoke about each other beyond work but it seems that everything appears to have changed now.</p>
<p>Shah Rukh, who had dinner at Aamir&rsquo;s 52nd birthday&nbsp;along with Netflix CEO and his team last week being among the guests has been spending a lot of time with Amir Khan lately, which created abuzz that they&rsquo;re teaming up for a project.</p>
<p>However, For Shah Rukh Khan, there is nothing unusual about their meetings. He also said that there are no hints towards a collaboration.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/image%20(2).jpg" alt="" width="467" height="331" /></p>
<p>King Khan also said that he has been &ldquo;personally&rdquo; meeting the <em>Dangal</em> star for years, but it&rsquo;s only now that their get-togethers are reported by the media.</p>
<p>SRK while talking about his meetings with Amir Khan said, &ldquo;We don&rsquo;t talk work&hellip; We haven&rsquo;t spoken on work for years. I think he&rsquo;s just been in town and even I am here&hellip; So that&rsquo;s it! And from last two-three months, he has come home. So, no there is nothing work wise that we have discussed. Earlier also we used to meet personally and often. It&rsquo;s just that the media has started spotting us now. In fact, it&rsquo;s weird that everyone knows when we meet now,&rdquo;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[4 wanted criminals arrested in Hafizabad combing operation]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134719-4-wanted-criminals-arrested-in-Hafizabad-combing-operation?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 10:57:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134719-4-wanted-criminals-arrested-in-Hafizabad-combing-operation?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134719_110826_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>HAFIZABAD: Four wanted persons were arrested during raids under the countrywide operation Radd-ul-Fasaad in&nbsp;</strong><strong>different parts of the country Saturday.</strong></p>
<p>More than 25 suspects were arrested by law enforcement agencies during raids in residential areas.</p>
<p>The police arrested 14 people in a combing operation in Hafizabad's Kasoki, Jalalpur Bhattian, and Venikay Tarar areas.</p>
<p>"The arrested individuals include wanted criminals, drug peddlers, and three Afghan nationals," the police told Geo News. "We have recovered arms and ammunition from their possession."</p>
<p>Biometric verification of the details of 89 suspects was completed during the operation.</p>
<p>Four wanted criminals and 13 suspects were arrested by the police in a raid in Kacha and Manikara areas in Bhakkar.</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[First day of headcount begins in Karachi]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134716-First-day-of-headcount-begins-in-Karachi?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 10:10:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134716-First-day-of-headcount-begins-in-Karachi?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134716_102144_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI/ISLAMABAD: The first day of head count of the sixth population census commenced in 7000 blocks of Karachi Saturday.</strong></p>
<p>Enumerators completed 65% of house count in the first phase of the data collection exercise.</p>
<p>A representative of the Bureau of Statistics told Geo News that the house count exercise will be completed along with the headcount data collection in different areas of Karachi.</p>
<p>A central control room to monitor the data collection exercise was formed in the office of SP Gulberg, Central District.&nbsp;</p>
<p>Addressing a press conference yesterday in Islamabad, Chief Census Commissioner Asif Bajwa said no changes will be made to the data collection forms as per the Supreme Court's directives.&nbsp;</p>
<p>"The appointed officers are already in the field. Data for specially-abled and transgender persons will be manually recorded through new codes," said Bajwa. "Even the Supreme Court has accepted that it is impossible to change the forms at this stage."</p>
<p>The Chief Census Commissioner further said that due to the availability of armed forces for a lesser period of time, some important services were postponed. "The forces were made available for 10 days this time; last time we had their services available for 15 days," Bajwa said.&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title><![CDATA[MQM Pakistan demands withdrawal of Aug 22 cases]]></title>
				<link><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134708-MQM-Pakistan-demands-withdrawal-of-Aug-22-cases?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></link>
				<pubDate><![CDATA[Sat, 18 Mar 2017 07:32:00 +0000]]></pubDate>				
	            <guid><![CDATA[https://www.geo.tv/latest/134708-MQM-Pakistan-demands-withdrawal-of-Aug-22-cases?utm_source=chatbot-english&utm_medium=fb-messenger&utm_campaign=story-slug]]></guid>
	            <description>
	            	<![CDATA[<img src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/uploads/updates/2017-03-18/l_134708_024927_updates.jpg"/>]]>
	            	<![CDATA[<p><strong>KARACHI: Muttahida Qaumi Movement-Pakistan leader Farooq Sattar has demanded an end to cases against his party workers related to anti-national speech on August 22 last year.</strong></p>
<p>The senior MQM-Pakistan leader said this in a press conference at the party's PIB Colony headquarters after his release following a brief detention by police personnel in Karachi. "I can't say if it was an arrest or a visit to the police station," he said.</p>
<p>Without naming the MQM founder Altaf Hussain, Sattar said, &ldquo;We have practically implemented minus-one. If now our workers are not released from the politically motivated cases, our offices continue to remain sealed, and if the leader of Pakistan&rsquo;s fourth largest political party is treated in such a way, then people will get confused.&rdquo;</p>
<p>He added, &ldquo;We have created an opportunity. If support is not given to those who stand with Pakistan Zindabad then the people will be forced to think that the agenda is beyond minus-one.&rdquo;</p>
<p>The MQM-Pakistan chief reiterated that &ldquo;We took extraordinary steps on August 23, now the time has come to respect those measures,&rdquo; he added, &ldquo;there is a policy level confusion existing right now with regards to MQM-Pakistan. The label of this August 22 cases must not taken away from them.&rdquo;</p>
<p><span class="ImgWithCaption" style="width: 700px; background: #e7e7e7; display: inline-block; padding: 0 3px 6px;"><img title="null" src="https://www.geo.tv/assets/front/tiny_mce/source/farooq-sattar1.jpg" alt="Sattar waves at his supporters after he was released from police detention" width="700" height="400" /><br /><span class="imgDesc" style="font-size: 13px;">Sattar waves at supporters after being&nbsp;released from police detention</span></span></p>
<p>Sattar said the MQM workers present at the Karachi Press Club on August 22 are innocent as they were not aware of the content of the speech. &nbsp;</p>
<p>&ldquo;Justice must be served in favour of those who have disassociated from the Aug 22 speech,&rdquo; he said.</p>
<p>Speaking on the occasion, MQM leader Faisal Sabzwari said that baseless cases are also against Prime Minister Nawaz Sharif as well; he added that the &lsquo;political vultures&rsquo; who are considering MQM dead are mistaken.</p>
<p>Sattar`s press conference came after a dramatic series of&nbsp;events in which police detained the MQM-Pakistan leader, only to release him an hour later.</p>
<p>Following Sattar's release, the Rabita Committee announced that it would go ahead with its decision celebrate the party's 'Youm-e-Tasees' today, (March 18).</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>]]>
	            </description>
			</item>
		    </channel>
</rss>